(Howard:)until I found
his Twitter handle.
(Raj:)From there, it was easy to find
him on Instagram, Snapchat
(Raj:)and pretty much track
his every movement.
(Howard:)So if you think that's creepy,
you married the wrong guy.
(Bernadette:)Maybe I should marry Trent.
(Raj:)Yeah, like she
could get Trent.
(laughing)
(Dave:)This is delicious.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Dave:)Been a long time since
I had a home-cooked meal.
(Amy:)When you were married,
did your wife cook?
(Dave:)Not at first, no.
(Dave:)But when she began cheating
on me with a French chef,
(Dave:)she became quite the wiz
in t kitchen.
(Amy:)So, a little silver lining.
(Dave:)I suppose.
(Dave:)Yeah. Nothing takes the sting
out of a shattered life
(Dave:)like a properly-seasoned
bowl of onion soup.
(Dave:)How long have you,
uh, lived here?
(Amy:)About five years.
(Amy:)I'm actually thinking
of moving to a better place
(Amy:)now that I don't need
to be so close to...
(Amy:)Well, you know.
(Dave:)I do. The brilliant physicist
(Dave:)that I now know lives
in the area, not that I care.
(Amy:)Yeah. Anyway, he doesn't drive,
(Amy:)so, I pretty much had
to take him everywhere.